what's good YouTube bishop boy be got
back with another quick video I'm not
too much into miracles but this beard
product is doing his damn thing
bossman beer jelly now one of my
subscribers in one of my video told me
hey man you should give that beer jelly
a try now I had heard a few things about
beer jelly but hadn't really got a
chance to really give it a try and if
you guys are following me on instagram
you'll see that I posted a picture of
all the beard products that I received
on Christmas and this boss man beer
jelly was one of them now this beer
jelly costs $14.99 on Amazon this right
here is the magic scent and the scent on
this one is vanilla sandalwood bergamot
frankincense and patchouli now I've only
been using this product for like three
days but like I've told you guys in
other videos know your beer I don't need
two or three weeks of a product to know
that it works for me
my first time using it I woke up in the
morning I did my regular routine I went
in and set the timer on my coffee jumped
in the shower wet might be a real good
with the steam and water I got out the
shower
you know combing through my beard a
little bit and then I grabbed a boss man
beer jelly now I'm putting about a
nickel size amount in my hand it doesn't
really tell you how much to put so I go
back to the standard nickel size a month
I rub it into my beer evenly bottom of
my beer you know around the size of my
beer like I would do a beard oil or a
beard balm comb through it I grab my
metal pick I picked it out got ready for
work went outside into the elements now
I usually travel with my little legacy
comb every day I go to work this is in
my coat pocket
so I gets to work you know I've combed
through my beard my dad my beer just
really soft now keep in mind this is
about maybe 10 o'clock you know I just
got to work so I calling through my
beard like I always do when I get to
work growing myself up real good
okay damn it feel soft not making too
much of it twelve o'clock rolls around I
pull out the same comb hit it again
comb just glide and right for
my beer so I get all the work I do my
job whatever I'm doing around 3 o'clock
I pull out the same comb I go through it
again it's still going right through my
beer guys I'm filling it it's like super
soft now I don't know what the hell is
in this but this to me is a miracle
beard product and it also falls in the
same category as the bang for your buck
you get the four ounces of beer jelly
for $14.99 now everybody knows when you
buy your beer oils or your beer bombs
you're getting one beer oil for maybe
ten dollars ten to fifteen dollars
you're getting a beer bomb for the same
price with this bossman beer generally
you're getting four ounces for $14.99 so
this is going to last you for a long
time with just using a nickel sized
amount or less well I use beer oils and
beer bombs every day I get really good
results from using those products this
is the first time I'm getting a chance
to use this and already it's a
game-changer I can see myself using this
everyday of course I'm going to use my
beer oils and my beer bombs going
forward and my own opinion if you decide
to go through this beer journey it's all
about options
I mean beer oil and beer bong that's
what we use but just beer jelly this is
something new I don't need two or three
weeks of using a product I know my beer
I put this in my beer three
consecutive days and each day my beer
was extremely soft all day long I got
off work I went to the gym I came home
calling my beard again the call went
straight through my beer beer still feel
extremely soft with a good scent my girl
digs the prod up I dig the product so
bossman beer jelly you did your thing
now since it's getting late here I'm
going to go ahead and put something on
this is probably the perfect thing to do
it for your nighttime routine if you
don't want to use your beer oil your
beer bongs to go to bed throw this beer
jelly in there you should be all good it
has the little twist top so you just
twist it up
you see some came out they should really
call this bossman beard
preservative because it's better than a
jelly about a nickel a model and you see
how it comes out and a little goes a
long way it rubs in you can feel the
resistance so you know that there is
beeswax in it and this is the magic
scent they have two other scents I'll
put links in the description
rub it throughout your beard
making sure to get underneath get that
monster finish combing through it I
would highly recommend this product make
sure you guys follow the links in the
description and go check it out bossman
beer jelly is it a miracle I'll leave it
up to you
definitely an ultra firm as always guys
thanks for checking me out thanks for
all the support continue to Like comment
and subscribe when the videos and I
holla back peace